Amrendra Kumar

Physical Education Teachers & Football Coach



Personal details



Amrendra Kumar



amrendrakumar1995@gmail. com



+919716340351



H No 2b Gali No 5a Goyla Vihar New Delhi 110071 New Delhi



August 5, 1995



MALE



INDIAN

Skills

Proud owner of several certificates and trophies in Football



Immense interest, Passion, and love for the sport



Thorough knowledge about the rules and regulations of football



Experience in teaching the sport to beginners as well as professionals

Excellent communication, •••• planning, and analysis skills



Expert in imposing and maintaining discipline and



Profile

Accomplished and energetic worker with a sold history of achievement in youth development. Motivated leader with strong organizational and prioritization abilities. Handles tasks with accuracy and efficiency.

Motivated Football Coach with 5+Years of Mentoring and coaching student-athletes. Adheres to safety Guidelines to protect players and enhance teams'overall athletic abilities such as speed, Ball control, and physical strength. Dedicated to Developing atmosphere of team work and collaboration among players and coaches.

Employment

FOOTBALL COACH

Oct 2018 - Feb 2019

HAPPY MODEL SCHOOL

FOOTBALL COACH

Aug 2019 - Mar 2020

BASAWA INTERNATIONAL SCHOOL, DWARKA SECTOR-23 DELHI

ASSISTANT FOOTBALL COACH

Jul 2017 - Feb 2019

HOPS FC, Paprawat, Delhi

FOOTBALL COACH

Jul 2017 - Jun 2019

SLC Academy, DWARKA SECTOR-5

FOOTBALL COACH

May 2018 - Oct 2021

KICK FC, PALAM VIHAR, DELHI

FOOTBALL COACH

Dec 2018 - Present

3F ACADEMY, DWARKA SECTOR-23 DELHI

FOUNDER & FOOTBALL COACH

Mar 2020 - Present

SPARK FOOTBALL ACADEMY, GOYLA KHURD DELHI

Sports Teacher

Jul 2022 - Mar 2023

Govt. Sr. Sec School(Sports village Foundation), Gurugram Haryana

- Plan, organize, and execute weekly lesson plans Planned adaptive lessons keeping in mind mood and overall ability of the students. • Organized age appropriate sports/games that focus on teamwork and cooperation.
- Instruct students, using adapted physical education techniques, to improve physical fitness, gross motor skills, perceptual motor skills, or sports and game achievement.
- Maintain thorough student records to document attendance, participation, or progress, ensuring confidentiality of all

records. Assess students physical progress or needs.

Assist in screening or placement of students in adapted physical education programs. Provide students positive feedback to encourage them and help them

develop an appreciation for physical education

· Provide individual or small groups of students with adapted physical education instruction that meets desired physical needs or goals. • Establish and maintain standards of behavior to create safe, orderly, and effective environments for learning.

team's spirit
Setting Goals
Team Building

Languages

English •••••
HINDI

Hobbies

Playing Game

Reading Book

Listeing Music

References

SANJAY SINGH

Unison World School 9654080312

Uttam singh Negi

CRPF School, Delhi 9871491310

Ravinder

ITL School, Delhi 9999374787

Education

Bachelor's Degree

Jun 2017

DelhiUniversity

Bachelor's Degree in Physical Education

Jun 2021

Barkatullah University, MP

Certificates

AIFF 'C' COACHING CERTIFICATE COURSE Participation.

AIFF GRASS ROOTS LEADERS COURSE

AIFF 'D' COACHING CERTIFICATE COURSE.

WORLD COACHES BASIC LEVEL COURSE

CERTIFIED FITNESS TRAINER.

FUTSAL LEVEL1 ONLINE DIPLOMA COURSE

Achievements

- U-17 Football Team zonal Level Participation.
- Yoga State Level Participation.
- U-19 Boys Basketball State Level Participation.
- U-14 Korfball State level second Position.
- U-17 Korfball State level First Position.
- U-19 Korfball State level First Position.
- U-17 Netball state level participation.

Extracurricular activities

DIPLOMA IN COMPUTER APPLICATIONS & PROGRAMMING

FIRST AIDS, CPR & AED.